{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "headcount",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "blind date",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "the last|straw",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "minimize",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "datebook",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "headquarters",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "candidate",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "pineapple",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "toothpaste",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "toothbrush",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "beanbag",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "campfire",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "buttercup",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "brainwave",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "snowman",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "keyboard",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "shoplifter",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "airline",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "rainbow",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "pancake",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "airport",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "banknote",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "freebie",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "eyelid",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "cowhide",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "popstar",
      "pregunta": "26",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "earphones",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "season",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "manpower",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "farmland",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "pickpocket",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "armband",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "lighthouse",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "homesick",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "cashbox",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "reading between|the lines",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "pretty|please",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "fast|food",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "nice to|meet you",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "make up|for lost time",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "apple pie",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "crossroads",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "all over|again",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "hit below|the belt",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "reduction",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "scent",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "flat tire",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "storm|in a teacup",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "couch|potato",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "rat|race",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "forgive and|forget",
      "pregunta": "51",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "up for grabs",
      "pregunta": "52",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "credibility|gap",
      "pregunta": "53",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "skate on|thin ice",
      "pregunta": "54",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "trip around|the world",
      "pregunta": "55",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "head over|heels",
      "pregunta": "56",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "middle aged",
      "pregunta": "57",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "go up|in smoke",
      "pregunta": "58",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "safety|in numbers",
      "pregunta": "59",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "a friend|in need",
      "pregunta": "60",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "what goes up|must come down",
      "pregunta": "61",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "broken|promise",
      "pregunta": "62",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "green|with envy",
      "pregunta": "63",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "foreign|movie",
      "pregunta": "64",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "turn the|other cheek",
      "pregunta": "65",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "see|for yourself",
      "pregunta": "66",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "small talk",
      "pregunta": "67",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "tickled pink",
      "pregunta": "68",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "side show",
      "pregunta": "69",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "the wrong end|of the stick",
      "pregunta": "70",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "back to|square one",
      "pregunta": "71",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "too funny|for words",
      "pregunta": "72",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "for instance",
      "pregunta": "73",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "bewitch",
      "pregunta": "74",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "way|overpriced",
      "pregunta": "75",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "address",
      "pregunta": "76",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "too little|too late",
      "pregunta": "77",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "stretching|the truth",
      "pregunta": "78",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "spaceship",
      "pregunta": "79",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "keeping you|out of trouble",
      "pregunta": "80",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "to sum|it up",
      "pregunta": "81",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "sixth|sense",
      "pregunta": "82",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "better safe|than sorry",
      "pregunta": "83",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "one life|to live",
      "pregunta": "84",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "back in|five minutes",
      "pregunta": "85",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "a shot|in the dark",
      "pregunta": "86",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "working|over time",
      "pregunta": "87",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "cry all the|way to the bank",
      "pregunta": "88",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "barking up|the wrong tree",
      "pregunta": "89",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "the stakes|are high",
      "pregunta": "90",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "tulips",
      "pregunta": "91",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "no one|to blame",
      "pregunta": "92",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "leftovers",
      "pregunta": "93",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "jack in|the box",
      "pregunta": "94",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "down payment",
      "pregunta": "95",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "once in|a blue moon",
      "pregunta": "96",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "asleep at|the wheel",
      "pregunta": "97",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "coffee break",
      "pregunta": "98",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "quarterback",
      "pregunta": "99",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "back up",
      "pregunta": "100",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "fooling|around",
      "pregunta": "101",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "dr house",
      "pregunta": "102",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "dr dolittle",
      "pregunta": "103",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "a monkey|on your back",
      "pregunta": "104",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "a play|on words",
      "pregunta": "105",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "get in shape",
      "pregunta": "106",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "a kick|in the butt",
      "pregunta": "107",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "high seas",
      "pregunta": "108",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "put two and|two together",
      "pregunta": "109",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "somewhere over|the rainbow",
      "pregunta": "110",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "home is where|the heart is",
      "pregunta": "111",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "see eye|to eye",
      "pregunta": "112",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "look out|for number one",
      "pregunta": "113",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "right under|the nose",
      "pregunta": "114",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "over my|dead body",
      "pregunta": "115",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "hot under|the collar",
      "pregunta": "116",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "broken heart",
      "pregunta": "117",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "fat chance",
      "pregunta": "118",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "falling|temperature",
      "pregunta": "119",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Image Puzzles",
      "respuesta": "head in|the sand",
      "pregunta": "120",
      "categoria": "wuzzles"
    }
  ]
}
